Archibald MacLeish Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Archibald MacLeish Papers 1907-1981 1925-1970
MSS30932
MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982
20,000 items
61 containers plus 1 oversize
25 linear feet
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Poet, playwright, government official, and Librarian of Congress. Papers include correspondence reflecting MacLeish's relations with friends, literary colleagues, and government associates; notebooks (1919-1940s) containing drafts of poetry and prose; manuscript drafts of plays and radio broadcasts, and speeches, including those written for Franklin D. Roosevelt, Edward R. Stettinius, and Harry S. Truman; and notes and manuscripts for classroom lectures on modern poetry given by MacLeish at Harvard University (1949-1962).
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Acheson, Dean, 1893-1971--Correspondence.; Biddle, Francis, 1886-1968--Correspondence.; Bliven, Bruce, 1889-1977--Correspondence.; Boyd, Julian P. (Julian Parks), 1903-1980--Correspondence.; Boyle, Kay, 1902-1992--Correspondence.; Bundy, McGeorge--Correspondence.; Byrnes, James F. (James Francis), 1882-1972--Correspondence.; Canfield, Cass, 1897-1986--Correspondence.; Ciardi, John, 1916-1986--Correspondence.; Cohen, Benjamin V.--Correspondence.; Colum, Mary--Correspondence.; Colum, Padraic, 1881-1972--Correspondence.; Conant, James Bryant, 1893-1978--Correspondence.; Cowley, Malcolm, 1898-1989--Correspondence.; Davenport, Russell W. (Russell Wheeler), 1899-1954--Correspondence.; Donovan, William J. (William Joseph), 1883-1959--Correspondence.; Dos Passos, John, 1896-1970--Correspondence.; Duell, Charles H. (Charles Halliwell), 1905-1970--Correspondence.; Dunn, J. C. (James Churchill), 1871-1955--Correspondence.; Early, Stephen T. (Stephen Tyree), 1889-1951--Correspondence.; Evans, Luther Harris, 1902-1981--Correspondence.; Fadiman, Clifton, 1904-1999--Correspondence.; Farrar, John Chipman, 1896-1974--Correspondence.; Feller, A. H. (Abraham Howard), 1904-1952--Correspondence.; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965--Correspondence.; Grew, Joseph C. (Joseph Clark), 1880-1965--Correspondence.; Hanson, Haldore, 1912-1992--Correspondence.; Harris, Roy, 1898-1979--Correspondence.; Hemingway, Ernest, 1899-1961--Correspondence.; Hopkins, Harry L. (Harry Lloyd), 1890-1946--Correspondence.; Hull, Cordell, 1871-1955--Correspondence.; Ickes, Harold L. (Harold LeClair), 1874-1952--Correspondence.; Ingersoll, Ralph, 1900-1985--Correspondence.; Kane, R. Keith (Richmond Keith), 1900-1974--Correspondence.; Kintner, Robert E. (Robert Edmonds), 1909-1980--Correspondence.; Kirchwey, Freda--Correspondence.; Lee, Muna, 1895?-1965--Correspondence.; Linscott, Robert N. (Robert Newton), 1886-1964--Correspondence.; Lovett, Robert A. (Robert Abercrombie), 1895-1986--Correspondence.; Luce, Henry Robinson, 1898-1967--Correspondence.; MacLeish, Andrew, 1838-1928--Correspondence.; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982--Books and reading.; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982--Travels.; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982.; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982. J.B. 1958.; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982. Pot of earth. 1925.; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982. Streets in the moon. 1926.; MacLeish, Kenneth, 1894-1918--Correspondence.; Mann, Thomas, 1875-1955--Correspondence.; McCloy, John J. (John Jay), 1895-1989--Correspondence.; Mearns, David C. (David Chambers), 1899-1981--Correspondence.; Meyer, Eugene, 1875-1959--Correspondence.; Morgenthau, Henry, 1856-1946--Correspondence.; Mumford, Lewis, 1895-1990--Correspondence.; Murphy, Gerald, 1888-1964--Correspondence.; Murphy, Sara--Correspondence.; Nicolson, Harold, 1886-1968--Correspondence.; Pearce, Charles A., 1906-1970--Correspondence.; Pound, Ezra, 1885-1972--Correspondence.; Rodman, Selden, 1909-2002--Correspondence.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962--Correspondence.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945--Correspondence.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Rosenman, Samuel I. (Samuel Irving), 1896-1973--Correspondence.; Saint-John Perse, 1887-1975--Correspondence.; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967--Correspondence.; Sherwood, Robert E. (Robert Emmet), 1896-1955--Correspondence.; Spender, Stephen, 1909-1995--Correspondence.; Steinbeck, John, 1902-1968--Correspondence.; Stettinius, Edward R., Jr. (Edward Reilly), 1900-1949--Correspondence.; Stettinius, Edward R., Jr. (Edward Reilly), 1900-1949.; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1900-1965--Correspondence.; Stimson, Henry L. (Henry Lewis), 1867-1950--Correspondence.; Sweetser, Arthur, 1888-1968--Correspondence.; Tate, Allen, 1899-1979--Correspondence.; Thomson, Charles A. (Charles Alexander), 1893-1961--Correspondence.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972--Correspondence.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.; Untermeyer, Louis, 1885-1977--Correspondence.; Van Doren, Mark, 1894-1972--Correspondence.; Walker, Charles R. (Charles Rumford), 1893-1974--Correspondence.; Wallace, Henry A. (Henry Agard), 1888-1965--Correspondence.; Warburg, James P. (James Paul), 1896-1969--Correspondence.; Weeks, Edward, 1898-1989--Correspondence.; Welles, Sumner, 1892-1961--Correspondence.; Woollcott, Alexander, 1887-1943--Correspondence.
Organizations
Harvard University--Faculty.; Library of Congress--Officials and employees.; Library of Congress.
Subjects
American drama.; American literature.; American periodicals.; American poetry.; Americans--Europe.; Authors, American.; Authors--Political and social views.; Drama.; Literature.; Poetry, Modern.; Poetry.; World War, 1939-1945--United States.
Places
Europe--Intellectual life--20th century.; United States--Intellectual life--20th century.; United States--Politics and government--20th century.
Titles
Fortune.
Occupations
Dramatists.; Librarians of Congress.; Poets.; Public officials.
Acquisition Information
The papers of Archibald MacLeish (1892-1982), poet, playwright, government official, and Librarian of Congress, were given to the Library of Congress from 1939 to 1970 by MacLeish, who also bequeathed a subsequent series of deposits, 1970-1977, to the Library in 1982. The Library received additional material, 1934-2012, through gifts, transfers, deposit, and purchases from various sources, including material formerly held by MacLeish's estate.
Additional Description
The Archibald MacLeish Papers are described in Library of Congress Acquisitions: Manuscript Division, 1982, p. 29.
Transfers
Items have been transferred from the Manuscript Division to other custodial divisions of the Library. Photographs have been transferred to the Prints and Photographs Division. Audiocassettes have been transferred to the Recorded Sound Section of the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division. All transfers are identified in these divisions as part of the Archibald MacLeish Papers. Patrons are encouraged to contact these divisions in advance of a research visit.
Access and Restrictions
The papers of Archibald MacLeish are open to research. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1892, May 7 Born, Glencoe, Ill.
1915 A.B., Yale University, New Haven, Conn.
1916 Married Ada Hitchcock
1917 1919 Served in United States Army
1919 LL.B., Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
1920 1923 Member of Boston, Mass., law firm, Choate, Hall and Stewart
1923 1928 Moved to Paris, France, devoting time to travel and literature
1929 1938 Editor, Fortune magazine
1932 Pulitzer Prize in poetry
1939 1944 Librarian of Congress
1941 1942 Director, Office of Facts and Figures,; War Department
1942 1943 Assistant Director, Office of War Information, War Department
1944 American delegate, Conference of Allied Ministers of Education, London, England
1944 1945 Assistant secretary of state for cultural affairs
1945 Chairman, American delegation to London conference to draft constitution for UNESCO Participated in drafting of United Nations charter at the San Francisco Conference
1946 Chairman, American delegation to the First General Conference of UNESCO, Paris, France First American member, executive council of UNESCO
1949 1962 Boylston Professor of Rhetoric and Oratory, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
1953 Pulitzer Prize in poetry Bollingen Prize in poetry National Book Award in poetry
1953 1956 President, American Academy of Arts and Letters
1959 Pulitzer Prize in drama
1963 1967 Simpson lecturer, Amherst College, Amherst, Mass.
1977 Presidential Medal of Freedom
1978 National Medal for literature
1982, Apr. 20 Died, Boston, Mass.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Archibald MacLeish cover the period from 1907 to 1981, with the bulk of the material dated between 1925 and 1970. Although MacLeish gave most of his literary manuscripts to Yale University, the Library of Congress's collection is particularly rich in its assemblage of correspondence reflecting MacLeish's relationships with personal friends, literary colleagues, and government associates and in its holdings of MacLeish's notebooks containing the origins of some of his greatest poems. The papers also include notes, worksheets, and manuscript drafts which detail the development of several of MacLeish's plays as well as document the political and moral convictions which motivated the many speeches and radio broadcasts he made both before and during World War II. Notes and manuscripts also exist for a series of classroom lectures on the form and condition of modern poetry conducted by MacLeish while serving as Boylston Professor of Rhetoric and Oratory at Harvard University from 1949 to 1962.
Few items remain for the period prior to 1923 when MacLeish left the Boston law firm where he was employed to live in Europe, devoting his time to reading, travel, and writing poetry. The earliest material in the Correspondence series is that between MacLeish and his father, Andrew, while MacLeish was a student at Hotchkiss School and Yale University. There are also several letters from MacLeish's brother, Kenneth, whose death in action during World War I greatly affected the poet. Of additional interest are letters from personal friends, such as Robert Newton Linscott, editor at Houghton Mifflin Company, and Charles Rumford Walker, which reflect some of the personal and artistic struggles MacLeish encountered during his years abroad.
MacLeish was one of a number of American literary expatriates living in Europe between the wars, enjoying the advantages of a favorable monetary exchange rate and the camaraderie of sympathetic fellow artists and writers. Many of the friendships which MacLeish made during the 1920's continued through later years, and the Correspondence series contains substantive letters from Kay Boyle,; Ernest Hemingway,; Gerald and Sara Murphy, and Ezra Pound. Incoming letters are also included in the Subject File from those who, along with MacLeish, advocated the release of Pound from St. Elizabeth's Hospital, the mental institution in Washington, D.C., where the poet had been confined after he was declared incompetent to stand trial for treason at the end of World War II. Other writers, artists, and scholars with whom MacLeish corresponded include Julian P. Boyd,; John Ciardi,; James Bryant Conant,; Mary and Padraic Colum,; Malcolm Cowley,; John Dos Passos,; Roy Harris,; Thomas Mann,; Lewis Mumford,; Harold George Nicolson,; Saint-John Perse,; Carl Sandburg,; Robert E. Sherwood,; Stephen Spender,; John Steinbeck,; Allen Tate,; Louis Untermeyer,; Mark Van Doren, and Alexander Woollcott.
During the 1930's MacLeish became increasingly politicized and was outspoken in support of an American commitment to protect the liberal democratic principles which he felt were being threatened by the rise of fascism in Europe. Several of his verse plays for radio, such as Air Raid (1938), The American Story (1944), and The Fall of the City (1937), illustrate these national or democratic themes. Material for these dramatic voice productions is contained in the Literary File series.
MacLeish more fully explicated his political philosophy in a series of prose pieces written for various journals and magazines throughout the 1930s and 1940s as well as in the many radio broadcasts and speeches he made during the same period. Notes and manuscript drafts for the writings are contained in the Literary File, while similar documents for the broadcasts and speeches are located in the Speeches and Lectures File. The latter series also contains copies and drafts for speeches which MacLeish prepared for Franklin D. Roosevelt,; Edward R. Stettinius,; Harry S. Truman, and other government officials.
From 1929 to 1938 MacLeish worked as a writer and editor for Fortune magazine, accepting the position from Henry Robinson Luce on the understanding that his commitment to the new publishing venture would be limited to the extent that, having earned enough money to satisfy his needs, MacLeish could return whenever he wished to his newly-purchased farm in Conway, Massachusetts, to work on his own writing. The Correspondence series contains a separate file for Fortune magazine and MacLeish's correspondence with Henry Robinson Luce. Other colleagues and friends from the field of publishing with whom MacLeish corresponded include Bruce Bliven,; Cass Canfield,; Russell Wheeler Davenport,; Charles H. Duell,; Clifton Fadiman,; John Farrar,; Ralph Ingersoll,; Freda Kirchwey,; Robert A. Lovett,; Eugene Meyer,; Charles A. Pearce,; Selden Rodman, and Edward Weeks.
In 1939, President Franklin D. Roosevelt persuaded a reluctant MacLeish to accept what proved to be a controversial appointment as the ninth Librarian of Congress. MacLeish implemented a thorough reorganization of the Library's administrative offices, published the Quarterly Journal of the Library of Congress, and established the Library's series of poetry readings. Because of his managerial skills and political involvement, MacLeish was also asked to serve, concurrent with his Library position, as director of the Office of Facts and Figures and assistant director of the Office of War Information from 1941 to 1944. In 1944, after his resignation from the Library, MacLeish was appointed assistant secretary of state for cultural affairs, in which capacity he helped plan the establishment of the United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization. Although the Subject File contains headings for these government agencies, none of the files contains extensive amounts of material. Official documents produced by MacLeish in his capacity as public servant are more likely to be represented in the central files or archival records of the respective federal agency.
The Correspondence series contains correspondence and copies of memoranda with many of MacLeish's associates, as well as with public figures, both in and out of government, whom MacLeish came to know during the war years. Correspondents of interest include Dean Acheson,; Francis Biddle,; McGeorge Bundy,; James Francis Byrnes,; Benjamin V. Cohen,; William J. Donovan,; J. C. Dunn,; Stephen T. Early,; Luther Harris Evans,; A. H. Feller,; Felix Frankfurter,; Joseph C. Grew,; Haldore E. Hanson,; Harry Lloyd Hopkins,; Cordell Hull,; Harold L. Ickes,; R. Keith Kane,; Robert E. Kintner,; Muna Lee,; John Jay McCloy,; David C. Mearns,; Henry Morgenthau,; Eleanor Roosevelt,; Franklin D. Roosevelt,; Samuel Irving Rosenman,; Edward R. Stettinius,; Adlai E. Stevenson,; Henry Lewis Stimson,; Arthur Sweetser,; Charles A. Thomson,; Harry S. Truman,; Henry Agard Wallace,; James P. Warburg, and Sumner Welles.
The Literary File contains an extensive set of notes for a series of classroom lectures which MacLeish delivered at Harvard University from 1949 to 1962. The purpose of these lectures was to provide a theoretical and historical framework within which a student could analyze the structure of modern poetry. MacLeish emphasized the influence of certain poets as pivotal to the development of modern poetry, and the notes he kept are quite thorough, providing insight into his teaching techniques.
With time afforded him after his retirement from public service, MacLeish published several books of poetry, produced dramatic pieces for various media, and wrote prose works, including social and political commentary. The Literary File contains correspondence and manuscript material for collections of poems such as Actfive (1948) and New and Collected Poems, 1917-1976 (1976). Although files related to the individual poems listed in this series include some worthwhile records, many contain material of little value, in some cases nothing more than copies of poems typewritten by MacLeish.
MacLeish continued to produce verse plays for stage, radio, and television, and the Literary File contains important material relating to these dramatic productions. Manuscript drafts and worksheets are contained in the collection for MacLeish's Pulitzer Prize-winning play, J.B. (1958). Similar material, including correspondence, is also included for other dramas such as An Evening's Journey to Conway, Massachusetts (1967), The Great American Fourth of July Parade (1975), Herakles (1967), Scratch (1971), This Music Crept By Me Upon the Waters (1953), and The Trojan Horse (1952). The disorganized state of many of the manuscripts and worksheets contained throughout the collection is the result of MacLeish's work habits. Describing the state of disarray of a draft for one of his plays, MacLeish wrote that it “can't be put together because I work like the crab retreating ten steps to go forward two and thus getting nowhere.” (1)
The greatest literary treasure of the collection is a set of notebooks kept by MacLeish from 1919 through the 1940s located in the Literary File. Containing drafts of much of his poetry and prose, the notebooks help trace the creation and development of some of MacLeish's finest work. They also include notes about his travels and readings and his reflections about other writers and their conversations on literature.
A notebook kept by MacLeish in Paris for the years 1924-25 contains drafts and trial lines for poems later published in Streets in the Moon (1926), including Ars Poetica, and a partial version of the verse play, The Pot of Earth (1925). Additional works by MacLeish represented in other notebooks include The Happy Marriage (1924), The Hamlet of A. MacLeish (1928), New Found Land (1930), Conquistador (1932), Frescoes for Mr. Rockefeller's City (1933), Panic (1935), Public Speech (1936), The Fall of the City (1937), America Was Promises (1939), and Actfive (1948).
(1) J.B. drafts and worksheets, Box 27
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged in six series:
Correspondence, 1907-1981
Literary File, 1919-1978
Speeches and Lectures File, 1939-1978
Subject File, 1937-1971
Miscellany, 1918-1972
Additions, 1926-1981
Container List
- Correspondence, 1907-1981 (Box 1-23)
  Letters received and copies of letters sent, memoranda, telegrams, postcards, and miscellaneous enclosures.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent and chronologically therein.
  - “A” miscellaneous, 1939-1975, undated, (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - Acheson, David, 1942-1943, 1953
  - Acheson, Dean, 1940-1971, undated
  - Ackerman, Carl W., 1941-1944
  - Adamic, Louis, 1941-1944
  - Adams, Donald, 1942
  - Agar, Herbert, 1940-1944
  - Agee, James, 1936, 1942
  - Aldington, Richard, 1941
  - Aldrich, Winthrop W., 1940
  - Alice Mary, Princess, 1963-1967
  - Allen, Hervey, 1939, 1945
  - Allen, James, 1942-1944
  - Allen, Jay, 1942-1945
  - Alsop, Joseph W., 1938-1940
  - Anderson, Clinton, 1942-1943
  - Angell, James R., 1943-1945
  - Angle, Paul M., 1942-1944
  - Arciniegas, German, 1945
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 1940-1943, 1965
  - Atherton, Ray, 1940-1945
  - Auchincloss, James C., 1942-1944
  - Auden, Wystan H., 1939-1940
  - “B” miscellaneous, 1927-1976, undated, (9 folders) (Box 2)
  - Baillie, Hugh, 1944-1948
  - Baker, Carlos, 1965
  - Baldwin, Roger, 1946, 1968
  - Barnes, George A., 1942 (Box 3)
  - Barrett, Edward, 1945
  - Barry, Philip, 1935-1945
  - Barth, Alan, 1941-1943
  - Bartlett, Edward L., 1945
  - Bartlett, Margaret, 1940-1945
  - Baskin, Leonard, 1964
  - Bassiano, Marguerite de, 1940-1941
  - Batt, William, 1944-1945
  - Battle, Lucius D., 1963
  - Baukhage, H. R., 1945
  - Beach, Sylvia, 1933, 1940
  - Bell, Ulric, 1942-1945
  - Belmont, Eleanor, 1944, 1969
  - Benet, Laura, 1944
  - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1939-1942
  - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1942
  - Benton, William, 1945-1946
  - Berle, Adolf, 1940-1945
  - Berlin, Irving, 1941
  - Bethune, Mary McLeod, 1945
  - Biddle, Francis, 1940-1945, 1970
  - Bingham, Barry, 1941-1945
  - Birkett, Norman, 1942
  - Black, Hugo L., 1942-1944
  - Blitzstein, Marc, 1939
  - Bliven, Bruce, 1939-1945, 1967
  - Bloom, Sol, 1945
  - Bonnet, Henri, 1945-1946
  - Bowers, Claude G., 1944
  - Bowes-Lyon, David, 1943, 1954
  - Bowles, Chester, 1944
  - Bowman, Isaiah, 1944
  - Boyd, James, 1940-1945
  - Boyd, Julian P., 1941-1946, 1970-1974
  - Boyle, Kay, 1932-1944 (Box 4)
  - Braden, Spruille, 1940-1945
  - Brandeis, Louis, 1939-1940
  - Brickell, Herschel, 1942-1946
  - Bromfield, Louis, 1939-1942
  - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1940-1949
  - Brown, John Mason, 1938, 1963-1967
  - Brown, Prentiss M., 1941-1942
  - Bruce, Edward, 1939-1942
  - Buck, Pearl S., 1942, 1963
  - Buck, Philo M., Jr., 1944
  - Bullitt, William C., 1937-1940
  - Bundy, Harvey H, 1941-1945
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1940-1945, 1962-1965, 1975
  - Burnett, Whit, 1942-1945, undated
  - Burton, Richard, 1965, undated
  - Bush, Vannevar, 1944-1945
  - Butler, Harold, 1942-1945
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1941-1945
  - Byrd, Harry Flood (1887-1966), 1942
  - Byrd, Richard E., 1941
  - Byrnes, James Francis, 1945
  - “C” miscellaneous, 1922-1976, undated, (6 folders)
  - Caetani, Marguerite, undated (Box 5)
  - Cairns, Huntington, 1943-1945
  - Calder, Ritchie, 1944-1947
  - Campbell, Ishbel MacLeish (sister), 1937
  - Canby, Henry Seidel, 1941-1946
  - Canfield, Cass, 1940-1945, 1965
  - Canham, Erwin D., 1942-1943
  - Carlson, Richard, 1940-1944
  - Carr, Lewis F., 1940-1944
  - Carter, Hodding, 1939-1940
  - Casals, Pablo, 1961, 1969
  - Celler, Emanuel, 1934-1945
  - Chafee, Zachary, Jr., 1941, undated
  - Chambers, Whittaker, 1941
  - Chien, Tuan-Shang, 1941-1945
  - Childs, Marquis W., 1942
  - Church, Frank, 1967-1969
  - Ciardi, John, 1956-1977
  - Clapp, Verner, 1945
  - Clapper, Olive, 1944-1945
  - Clayton, William, 1944-1945
  - Cohen, Benjamin V., 1940-1945
  - Cohn, Alfred A., 1939-1945
  - Colum, Mary, 1940-1942
  - Colum, Padraic, 1939, 1957-1959
  - Commager, Henry S., 1941, 1950, undated
  - Conant, James Bryant, 1935-1946, undated
  - Connally, Tom, 1941-1945
  - Corcoran, Thomas G., 1940-1942
  - Corwin, Norman, 1939-1945
  - Coulter, Douglas, 1944
  - Cousins, Norman, 1942-1946
  - Cowles, Gardner, Jr., 1942-1944
  - Cowles, John, 1942-1944
  - Cowley, Malcolm, 1941-1945, 1957, 1974
  - Cox, Oscar, 1942-1946
  - Coy, Wayne, 1942
  - Cummings, Edward Estlin, 1948-1949
  - “D” miscellaneous, 1937-1966, undated
    - “Da-Dom”, (2 folders)
    - “Don-Dy”, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Dahlberg, Edward, 1958
  - Damrosch, Walter, 1945
  - Dana, Marshall N., 1945
  - Daniels, Jonathan, 1940-1945
  - Daniels, Josephus, 1941-1944
  - Davenport, Basil, 1941
  - Davenport, Russell Wheeler, 1939-1944
  - Davidson, Jo, 1944-1945
  - Davis, Elmer, 1939-1954
  - Davis, Norman H., 1941-1942
  - Delano, Frederic A., 1941-1944
  - Delano, William Adams, 1941-1945
  - Denny, George V., Jr., 1942-1945
  - Dern, John, 1939-1943
  - De Voto, Bernard, 1940
  - Dickey, John, 1944-1945, 1968